A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Living at Home Program, SG 1, Series 24 FA296
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence - With Advisory Committee, May-December 1985 (Box 18, Folder 171)
- General Correspondence - With Advisory Committee, January 1986-December 1987 (Box 18, Folder 172)
- General Correspondence - With Sponsors and Endorsers, December 1985-February 1986 (Box 18, Folder 173)
- Annual Meetings - Boston, Massachusetts, April 21-23, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 174)
- Annual Meetings - San Francisco, California, May 9-11, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 175)
- Annual Meetings - Chicago, Illinois, May 15-17, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 176)
- Living At Home Newsletters, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 177)
- Applications (A), undated (Box 19, Folder 178)
  Scope and Contents note
  All Souls Church; Washington, D.C. Allen County Council on Aging; Fort Wayne, Indiana Area Agency on Aging; Akron, Ohio
- Applications (A), undated (Box 19, Folder 179)
  Allentown Area for the Aging; Allentown, Pennsylvania Area Agency on Aging of Broward County; Fort Lauderdale, Florida
- Applications (A), undated (Box 19, Folder 180)
  Area Office on Aging of Northwestern Ohio, Inc.; Toledo, Ohio Associated Catholic Charities; New Orleans, Louisiana
- Applications (A-B), undated (Box 19, Folder 181)
  Atlanta Regional Commission; Atlanta, Georgia Dr. Gertrude A. Barber Center; Erie, Pennsylvania Bethel New Life, Inc.; Chicago, Illinois
- Applications (C), undated (Box 19, Folder 182)
  Cabrini Medical Center; New York, New York Caddo Council on Aging, Inc.; Shreveport, Louisiana
- Applications (C), undated (Box 19, Folder 183)
  Cardinal Ritter Institute (2 copies); St. Louis, Missouri
- Applications (C), undated (Box 19, Folder 184)
  Catholic Charities Inc.; Los Angeles, California Catholic Social Services; San Francisco, California
- Applications (C), undated (Box 20, Folder 185)
  Center for Gerontological Education; Notre Dame, Indiana Center Boston Elder Services, Inc.; Boston, Massachusetts
- Applications (C), undated (Box 20, Folder 186)
  Central Indiana Council on Aging, Inc. (3 copies); Indianapolis, Indiana
- Applications (C), undated (Box 20, Folder 187)
  Church Hospital; Baltimore, Maryland Coalition on Home Care and Elderly Life Management of Greater Richmond; Richmond, Virginia Coastline Elderly Services, Inc.; New Bedford, Massachusetts College of Nursing: University of Illinois at Chicago; Chicago, Illinois Columbia Club; Seattle, Washington
- Applications (C), undated (Box 20, Folder 188)
  Community Action Committee/Office on Aging; Knoxville, Tennessee Community Agency for Senior Citizens, Inc.; Staten Island, New York Community Council of the Capitol Region, Inc.; Hartford, Connecticut Community Health Services, Nazareth Home Health Agency; Louisville, Kentucky Coney Island Hospital, New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation; Brooklyn, New York
- Applications (C), undated (Box 20, Folder 189)
  Connecticut Community Care, Inc.; Bristol, Connecticut Coordinated Boy Services Program, Jewish Community Centers Association; St. Louis, Missouri Council of Community Services of Northeastern New York, Inc.; Albany, New York
- Applications (C-D), undated (Box 20, Folder 190)
  Council of Elders, Inc.; Roxbury, Massachusetts Department of Human Services, Adult and Aging Services; Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Detroit Area Agency on Aging, Detroit, Michigan
- Applications (E), undated (Box 21, Folder 191)
  East Central Florida Regional Planning Council; Winter Park, Florida Easter Seal Society of Dade County, Inc.; Miami, Florida Eastern Washington Area Agency on Aging; Spokane, Washington Ecumenical Ministries of Oregon and Good Samaritan Health Services; Portland, Oregon
- Applications (E), undated (Box 21, Folder 192)
  The Educational Alliance, Inc.; New York, New York Elwyn Institutes - National Rehabilitation Center; Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Episcopal Community Churches, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
- Applications (F), undated (Box 21, Folder 193)
  Family Service, Inc.; Fort Worth, Texas Family Service Centers of Pinellas County; St. Petersburg, Florida Family Service of Greater Boston; Boston, Massachusetts
- Applications (F), 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 194)
  Federation for Community Planning; Cleveland, Ohio Flint Area Health Foundation; Flint, Michigan
- Applications (F), undated (Box 21, Folder 195)
  Forsyth County Council for Older Adults, Inc.; Winston-Salem, North Carolina Fresno-Madera Area Agency of Aging; Fresno, California
- Applications (G), undated (Box 21, Folder 196)
  Geriatric Resources Corporation; Kansas City, Kansas Greater Springfield Senior Services, Inc.; Springfield, Massachusetts Guiding Hand Centers, Inc.; Warren, Michigan
- Applications (H), undated (Box 22, Folder 197)
  Health Alliance Plan - Health Facilities Administration; Detroit, Michigan Home-Med North, Inc.; Chicago, Illinois The Hospital of the Good Samaritan; Los Angeles, California The Hudson Guild; New York, New York
- Applications (I), undated (Box 22, Folder 198)
  Illinois Masonic Medical Center; Chicago, Illinois Inter Community Action, Inc.; Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Interfaith Conference of Metropolitan Washington, Washington, D.C. Inwood Council on Aging, Inc./Washington Heights; New York, New York
- Applications (J), undated (Box 22, Folder 199)
  Jamaica Service Program for Older Adults, Inc.; Jamaica, New York City of Jersey, Jersey City, New York
- Applications (J), undated (Box 22, Folder 200)
  Jewish Association for Services for the Aged (JASA); New York, New York The Jewish Community Federation of Louisville, Inc.; Louisville, Kentucky Association of Jewish Family and Children's Agencies; New York, New York Jewish Family and Children's Services; Baltimore, Maryland
- Applications (J), undated (Box 22, Folder 201)
  Jewish Family Services of Los Angeles; Los Angeles, California The Jewish Home and Hospital for Aged; New York, New York
- Applications (J-K), undated (Box 22, Folder 202)
  The Johns Hopkins Hospital; Baltimore, Maryland Kings County Hospital; Brooklyn, New York Kingsbrook Jewish Medical Center; Brooklyn, New York
- Applications (L), undated (Box 22, Folder 203)
  Lackawanna County Area Agency on Aging; Scranton, Pennsylvania League of Older Americans, Inc.; Roanoke, Virginia The Lincoln Fellowship of Churches; Lincoln, Nebraska
- Applications (L), undated (Box 23, Folder 204)
  Long Beach Community Hospital; Long Beach, California The Lutheran Home at Germantown; Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Lutheran Medical Center; Brooklyn, Pennsylvania
- Applications (M), undated (Box 23, Folder 205)
  Manhattan Plaza Foundation, Inc.; New York, New York Mecklenburg County Health Department; Charlotte, North Carolina Mercy-Douglas Center, Inc.; Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Mercy Health System of Western New York; Buffalo, New York
- Applications (M), undated (Box 23, Folder 206)
  Mercy Midlands; Omaha, Nebraska Metro Date County Elderly Services Division; Miami, Florida Metropolitan Baptist Church; Detroit, Michigan Metropolitan Commission on Aging; Syracuse, New York
- Applications (M-N), undated (Box 23, Folder 207)
  Montefiore Medical Center; New York, New York Moses Taylor Hospital; Scranton, Pennsylvania Neighborly Senior Services, Inc.; Clearwater, Florida New Center Community Mental Health Services; Detroit, Michigan
- Applications (N), undated (Box 23, Folder 208)
  New England Institute for Healthcare Services Research, Inc.; Boston, Massachusetts New Orleans Council on Aging; New Orleans, Louisiana New York Foundation for Senior Citizens, Inc.; New York, New York New York City Department for the Aging; New York, New York
- Applications (N-O), undated (Box 23, Folder 209)
  Northeast Florida Area Agency on Aging, Inc.; Jacksonville, Florida Northwestern Illinois Area Agency on Aging; Rockford, Illinois Office of Elder Affairs; Worcester, Massachusetts Office of Senior Citizens' Activities; Birmingham, Alabama
- Applications (O-P), undated (Box 24, Folder 210)
  Our Lady of Mercy Medical Center; Bronx, New York Park Duvalle Community Health Center; Louisville, Kentucky PATH (People Acting to Help), Inc.; Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Philadelphia Corporation for Aging; Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
- Applications (P), undated (Box 24, Folder 211)
  Philadelphia Home Care; Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Pierce County Area Agency on Aging; Tacoma, Washington Protestant Community Services; Rockford, Illinois The Public Health Nursing Association of Des Moines; Des Moines, Iowa
- Applications (R), undated (Box 24, Folder 212)
  RAIN, Inc. (Regional Aid for Interim Needs, Inc.); Bronx, New York REAL Services of St. Joseph County, Inc.; South Bend, Indiana Resurrection Hospital; Chicago, Illinois
- Applications (R), undated (Box 24, Folder 213)
  Rhode Island Department of Elderly Affairs (DEA); Providence, Rhode Island City of Richmond Long Term Care Coordinating Committee; Richmond, Virginia
- Applications (R-S), undated (Box 24, Folder 214)
  Ridgewood Bushwick Senior Citizens Council, Inc.; Brooklyn, New York Riverdale Neighborhood House, Inc.; Bronx, New York Salt Lake County Aging Services; Salt Lake City, Utah San Fernando Valley Interfaith Community; Van Nuys, California
- Applications (S), undated (Box 24, Folder 215)
  San Joaquin County Department of Aging, Children's and Community Services; Stockton, California City of Seattle, Department of Human Resources; Seattle, Washington Sedgwick County Department on Aging; Wichita, Kansas Selfhelp Community Services; New York New York
- Applications (S), undated (Box 24, Folder 216)
  Senior Action, Inc; Greenville, South Carolina Senior Citizens Department; Detroit, Michigan Senior Citizen's East, Inc.; Louisville, Kentucky Senior Citizens Savannah - Chatham County, Inc.; Savannah, Georgia
- Applications (S), undated (Box 25, Folder 217)
  Senior Citizens Services, Inc.; Mobile, Alabama Senior Workers' Action Program, Inc.; Akron, Ohio
- Applications (S), undated (Box 25, Folder 218)
  SHINE/Glendale Memorial Hospital and Health Center; Glendale, California South Central Connecticut Agency on Aging, Inc.; West Haven, Connecticut
- Applications (S), undated (Box 25, Folder 219)
  South Shore Hospital and Medical Center (2 copies); Miami Beach, Florida
- Applications (S), undated (Box 25, Folder 220)
  Southeast Tennessee Area Office on Aging/Family & Children's Services of Chattanooga, Inc.; Chattanooga, Tennessee Southwestern Connecticut Agency on Aging; Bridgport, Connecticut Southwestern Indiana Regional Council on Aging, Inc.; Evansville, Indiana
- Applications (S), undated (Box 25, Folder 221)
  St. Alexis Hospital Medical Center/AlexiCARE; Cleveland, Ohio St. Andrew's Lutheran Church; Chicago, Illinois St. Anthony's Hospital, Inc.; St. Petersburg, Florida
- Applications (S), undated (Box 25, Folder 222)
  St. Elizabeth Hospital Medical Center; Youngstown, Ohio St. Joseph Villa; Salt Lake City, Utah St. Luke's Hospital; New Bedford, Massachusetts
- Applications (S-T), undated (Box 25, Folder 223)
  Sun City Area Community Council; Sun City, Arizona Synod of Southern California and Hawaii, Asian Human Care Centers; Los Angeles, California Thomas Jefferson University Hospital; Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Topeka-Shawnee County Health Department; Topeka, Kansas
- Applications (T-U), undated (Box 26, Folder 224)
  City of Tulsa/Tulsa Area Agency on Aging; Tulsa, Oklahoma United Charities of Chicago; Chicago, Illinois United Community Centers, Inc.; Fort Worth, Texas United Home Care; Cincinnati, Ohio United Methodist Neighborhood Services; Philadelphia, Pennsylvania United Planning Organization; Washington, D. C.
- Applications (U), undated (Box 26, Folder 225)
  United Way (Area Agency Unit); Dayton, Ohio United Way of Pulaski County, Inc.; Little Rock, Arkansas United Way of Wyandotte County, Inc.; Kansas City, Kansas
- Applications (U-V), undated (Box 26, Folder 226)
  University of Maryland at Baltimore; Baltimore, Maryland Virginia Mason Hospital; Seattle, Washington Volunteers of America Colorado Branch; Denver, Colorado
- Applications (W,Y), undated (Box 26, Folder 227)
  Washington Health Care Corporation; Washington, D. C. Washington Urban League, Inc.; Washington, D. C. World Medical Relief, Inc.; Detroit, Michigan City of Yonkers, Office for the Aging; Yonkers, New York
- Application Review - Official Letters of Intent, undated (Box 26, Folder 228)
- Application Review - Guidelines for Application Review, undated (Box 26, Folder 229)
- Application Review - First Grantee Selection Meeting, April 1, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 230)
- Application Review - First Round Results, April 9, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 231)
- Application Review - Schedule for Semi-Finalist Review, undated (Box 26, Folder 232)
- Application Review - Application Score Sheets - Reader #1-4, undated (Box 26, Folder 233)
- Application Review - Application Score Sheets - Reader #5-7, undated (Box 27, Folder 234)
- Application Review - Application Score Sheets - Reader #8-10, undated (Box 27, Folder 235)
- Application Review - Application Score Sheets - Reader #11-13, undated (Box 27, Folder 236)
- Application Review - Application Score Sheets - Reader #14-15, undated (Box 27, Folder 237)
- Application Review - Application Score Sheets - Reader #AC1-AC3, undated (Box 27, Folder 238)
- Application Review - Application Score Sheets - Reader #AC4-AC6, undated (Box 27, Folder 239)
- Application Review - Application Score Sheets - Reader #AC7-AC9, undated (Box 28, Folder 240)
- Application Review - Application Score Sheets - Reader #AC10-AC11, undated (Box 28, Folder 241)
- Application Review - Application Score Sheets - Reader #AC12-AC14, undated (Box 28, Folder 242)
- Application Review - Application Score Sheets, April 21-25, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 243)
- Application Review - Application Score Sheets, April-May 1986 (Box 28, Folder 244)
- Application Review - Application Score Sheets, May 6-9, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 245)